[Music]
[音乐]
all right hi everybody
大家好
I am going to we have very little time
我要去的时候很少
as always we have very little time so we
一如既往，我们只有很少的时间，所以我们
dispense with important business first
首先放弃重要的业务
and then we'll get to the talk I want to
然后我们去谈我想要的
get a selfie I need you all to pretend
得到自拍照，我需要你们所有人假装
like you're happy and just and just say
就像你很快乐，公正，只是说
open-source when I say open-source and
当我说开源和
we'll take a photo together and it's
我们一起拍张照片
gonna be awesome okay so okay okay
会很棒的，好吧，好吧，好吧
ready steady open sores and Othar this
准备好稳定的疮和奥萨尔这
open sores thank you my friends I
疮疮，谢谢你，我的朋友们，我
appreciate that thanks so much for
非常感谢你
coming how are you oh that was too fine
来你好吗哦，那太好了
you're in I I kind of understand that I
你在我的那种II
mean have you seen outside it's paradise
意思是你在天堂之外见过
and here we're you know I love I love
在这里我们你知道我爱我爱
software as much as anybody can but
尽可能多的软件，但是
beautiful Barcelona is all around us so
美丽的巴塞罗那在我们身边
we are we are a very little time so I
我们是我们只有很少的时间，所以我
want to encourage you to take note of
想鼓励您注意
this slide you can see at the top
您可以在顶部看到此幻灯片
there's a git repository that repository
有一个git仓库
is actually for an eight-hour online
实际上是在线八个小时
training that I do it's eight hours of
我训练的时间是八个小时
training and there's lots of stuff there
培训，那里有很多东西
including what we're gonna talk about
包括我们要谈论的内容
today but also a lot more so you know
今天，还有更多，所以你知道
you can have all that for free I'm sure
你可以免费得到所有这些
you'll it's pretty kind of you know once
你会很像你知道的
understand the basics we're gonna talk
了解我们要讲的基础知识
about testing we're gonna go through a
关于测试，我们将要通过
lot of stuff today okay the goal is to
今天有很多东西可以，目标是
go through a lot of stuff but some
经历很多东西，但有些
important parts that we're gonna cover
我们要覆盖的重要部分
for only a few minutes are actually
实际上只有几分钟
going to be covered in much more depth
将被更深入地覆盖
by Andy Wilkinson he's got a talk on
由安迪·威尔金森（Andy Wilkinson）发表
testing as well in spring and that's a
在春季进行测试，这是一个
very good talk I would you know that's
很好的谈话，我想你知道
the talk that if we could merge this
如果我们可以合并这个话题
together and include his and then and
在一起，包括他的然后
then include mine around that that would
然后将我的周围包括在内
be a good story but I recommend you
是个好故事，但我推荐你
enjoy this and then we're gonna we're
享受这个，然后我们要
gonna go through a lot of stuff and then
要经历很多事情，然后
you go see Andy wilkinson's talk cuz
你去看看安迪·威尔金森的演讲
that'll have the details on a particular
上面会有关于特定细节的信息
segment of this discussion okay a little
这段讨论还可以
bit about me my name is Josh long I work
关于我的一点名字我叫乔希
on the spring team I'm on Twitter how
在春季团队中，我在Twitter上如何
many of you just curious aren't twitter
你们很多人只是好奇不是推特
2019 i always wonder about this twitter
2019我一直想知道这个推特
twitter 2009
2009年推特
kiin twitter twitter all right the rest
kiin twitter twitter其余的一切都很好
of you what are you doing get on it get
你在做什么你就得到它
on Twitter it's a good place to be it's
在Twitter上，这是个好地方
the new IRC it's for the developers that
新的IRC是针对开发人员的
drive the open source that power of your
驱动开源，您的力量
business are and it's fine I'm also
生意很好，我也很好
available by email how many of you have
可以通过电子邮件获取有多少人
email email is email a thing do you use
电子邮件电子邮件是您使用的东西
email I don't I'm not really a big email
电子邮件，我不是，我不是很大的电子邮件
person but on the other hand I prefer it
人，但另一方面我更喜欢
to slack right I have a brand new
放松吧，我有一个全新的
MacBook Pro with 32 gigs of ram 32 gigs
MacBook Pro配备32个演出，32个演出
of ram that's a that's enough to run
公羊的那是足以运行
almost a slack right it's a big deal so
几乎是松弛，这很重要
that that's exciting for me I still
那仍然令我兴奋
prefer email to that write a little bit
偏爱电子邮件一点点写
about me I work on the spring team you
关于我，我在 The Spring Team 工作
know that's cool I'm very lucky there I
知道那很酷，我在那里很幸运
went to China and they made a little toy
去了中国，他们做了一个小玩具
out of me that's nice
从我身上出来很好
I have training videos on Safari these
我在Safari上有这些培训视频
are online you can find all sorts of
在线，您可以找到各种各样的
different content there these are sort
这些是不同的内容
of in-depth discussions of of different
不同的深入讨论
topics and these are usually you know
话题，这些通常是你知道的
four or five six seven eight hours of
四或五六七八小时的
content I've got a book called cloud
内容我有一本书叫云
native Java all about how to build
本机Java关于如何构建
applications that survive and thrive in
能够在其中生存和发展的应用程序
the cloud I've got a podcast called a
我有一个叫做a的播客
beautiful podcast every Friday you can
您可以在每个星期五进行美丽的播客
go to Google Play or of iTunes or
转到Google Play或iTunes或
whatever whatever find podcasts are
不论发现什么播客
downloaded you can find that their
下载您可以找到他们的
screencasts every Wednesday so every
每个星期三都进行截屏
Wednesday I do a new screencast I look
星期三，我看了一个新的截屏视频
at some part of the spring ecosystem so
在春季生态系统的某个部分
the thing that we did yesterday was all
我们昨天做的事情就是全部
about using Kafka from spring batch
关于从Spring Batch处理中使用Kafka
which i think is super interesting and
我认为这非常有趣，
I've got a new book oh you want that
我有一本新书哦，你想要那本书
photo okay and we've got a new book a
照片还可以，我们有一本新书
new book called reactive spring and this
新书叫做反应性Spring
is self-published it's on lean pub you
是自我发布的，它在您的精益酒吧中
can find it there right now you can
现在可以在那里找到它
already start reading it there's already
已经开始阅读它了
200 pages of stuff and I'm gonna add
200页的内容，我要添加
more if you buy it now it's cheap and
如果您现在购买，价格还会更高，而且
then you can you know when the final
那么你可以知道当最后
book comes out you get the final edition
书出来了，你得到了最终版
but you don't pay any extra cost you buy
但您不支付任何额外费用
the cheap price now and then it's
便宜的价格，然后它是
cheaper than the final Edition cost
比最终版便宜
later so all this stuff all this stuff
后来所有这些东西所有这些东西
so why would I spend time with you today
那我今天为什么要和你在一起
if I could spend time talking about
如果我能花时间谈论
anything why would I talk about testing
什么我为什么要谈论测试
and I think testing is one of those
我认为测试是其中之一
parts of the sort of spectrum the
频谱的一部分
continuum that we
我们的连续体
have to deal with that we don't really
必须处理我们不是真的
think about until we get to a place
考虑一下，直到我们到达一个地方
where we need testing what I mean by
我们需要测试我的意思的地方
that is we have been talking about micro
那就是我们一直在谈论微
services and cloud computing and
服务和云计算以及
continuous delivery and all these things
持续交付和所有这些东西
that motivate or rather they support the
激励或更确切地说，他们支持
goal of building software faster of
更快构建软件的目标
moving value from concept all the way
始终从概念中转移价值
down to customer faster and that's been
更快地服务于客户，这已经
something that people in general have
人们普遍拥有的东西
been talking about for the last ten
最近十年来一直在谈论
years I've certainly been talking about
我当然一直在谈论
it a lot
很多
micro services and continuous delivery
微服务和持续交付
and agile and all these things are in in
和敏捷，所有这些东西都在
service of deploying software to
将软件部署到
business you know to deploying business
您对部署业务了解的业务
value to production faster when you get
获得价值时更快地实现生产价值
down that path one thing that you very
沿着那条路，你非常
quickly discover is that in order to do
很快发现是为了做
this in order to really take advantage
为了真正利用
of this fast movement you need to have
这种快速运动需要
safety as well right anybody anybody can
任何人都可以安全
drive a real fast car straight into a
开一辆真正的快车
wall that's not very useful speed by
墙不是很有用的速度
itself isn't very useful what you need
本身不是很有用，您需要什么
is something to sort of calibrate that
是某种可以校准的东西
to to measure to meter it and that is a
要测量以计量它，这是一个
test harness right in our case we want
在我们想要的情况下测试线束
validation that every time we introduce
每次我们介绍的验证
a change and as quickly as we introduce
改变并尽快介绍
a change that we know that that change
我们知道这种变化的变化
hasn't broken anything that's what we
没有破坏我们所要做的
mean by having a safety so we want to
意味着拥有安全性，所以我们想要
move quickly and safely to production
快速安全地进行生产
and I think testing really is the most
我认为测试确实是最重要的
important part of that of that last word
最后一句话的重要部分
safely so when we talk about testing I
安全，所以当我们谈论测试时
think most of us are pretty familiar
认为我们大多数人都很熟悉
with the absolute basics with respect to
绝对的基础
testing a monolithic application right
测试整体应用程序权限
but I think things become more
但我认为事情变得越来越多
interesting when you start moving into a
当你开始进入一个有趣的
distributed systems world where you see
您所见的分布式系统世界
that now things become distributed and
现在事情变得分散了
now they require integration and the
现在他们需要整合，
problem with this is that as you move to
问题在于当您移至
a micro services world you find that
一个微服务世界，您会发现
increasingly large amounts of your
您的数量越来越多
codebase become integration tests it's
代码库成为集成测试
harder to validate what you're doing in
很难验证您在做什么
this new world and so what we want to do
这个新世界，所以我们想做什么
is we want to get fast feedback the goal
是我们要获得快速反馈的目标吗
here is to optimize for fast feedback
这是为了快速反馈而优化
how quickly can i deploy an idea and get
我能多快部署一个想法并获得
the results from that idea and then
这个想法的结果，然后
incorporate their feedback from that
结合他们的反馈
into the next iteration right if I'm
进入下一个迭代，如果我是
spending all my time we
花我所有的时间，我们
for application servers to start up or
为应用服务器启动或
if I'm spending all my time waiting for
如果我花所有的时间等待
the C++ code to compile if I'm spending
我花钱时要编译的C ++代码
all my time waiting for the integration
我所有的时间都在等待整合
code to run on the on the in CI
在CI上运行的代码
environment then I'm not gonna I'm not
环境，那我就不会
going to be moving quickly I'll be
会很快移动，我会
kicked out of the zone right this is a
踢出区域，这是一个
problem right we want to we want to stay
问题权，我们想要，我们想要留下
perpetually in the zone want to enjoy
永久在该地区想享受
that sense that we're moving forward
感觉我们正在前进
we're making progress and that as we
我们正在进步，而随着我们
move forward we're getting good results
向前迈进，我们取得良好的结果
and this by the way gets us to the next
顺便说一下，这使我们进入了下一个
point this desire to stay in the zone
指出留在该区域的愿望
does this desire to constantly have
这种渴望不断
feedback as opposed to having these
反馈而不是拥有这些
rivers of productivity and then long
生产力之河，然后漫长
periods of just waiting and waiting and
只是等待和等待的时期
waiting the that goal that feeling that
等待那个目标，那种感觉
we're moving quickly that's not just a a
我们正在迅速行动，而不仅仅是
a wish it should be a requirement it
希望这是一个要求
should be absolutely critical to the way
对方式绝对关键
you approach software and so this is why
您使用软件，这就是为什么
we're gonna talk about testing as well
我们还将讨论测试
we're gonna talk about test-driven
我们将谈论测试驱动
development okay today we're gonna talk
发展很好，今天我们要谈
about test-driven development and the
关于测试驱动的开发和
idea behind test-driven development is
测试驱动开发背后的想法是
very simple you write the tests before
很简单，您之前编写测试
you write the business logic and this is
您编写业务逻辑，这是
important because I hope most of your
重要，因为我希望您的大多数
writing tests are all of you writing
写作测试都是你们写作
tests who's who's writing tests okay I
测试谁在写谁，测试我好
don't see all hands so you know maybe
没有看到所有的手，所以你也许知道
you have a job like me where you just
你有像我这样的工作
write simple stuff on stage and it's
在舞台上写一些简单的东西
mostly about the ASCII art work you know
主要是关于您知道的ASCII艺术作品
maybe I don't know but but you should be
也许我不知道，但是你应该
writing tests unless you're like Chuck
除非你像查克一样，否则就写测试
Norris or something right you should be
诺里斯（Norris）或您应有的权利
writing tests and it's good to write
编写测试，写起来很好
tests afterwards but it can be a bit a
之后进行测试，但可能会有点
bit depressing it can feel like a chore
有点压抑的感觉就像是家务
so what we want is to get to a place
所以我们想要去的地方
where we can write code and deliver
在这里我们可以编写代码并交付
value into production and we can stay in
重视生产，我们可以留在
the zone and so when we talk about the
该区域，所以当我们谈论
zone when we talk about test-driven
当我们谈论测试驱动时
development tester Mandela man it's very
开发测试员Mandela男人
simple idea you write the test first and
一个简单的想法，你先写测试，然后
then you write the production code that
然后编写生产代码，
satisfies the test so you write a broken
满足测试，所以您写了一个破
test and then you write a little bit of
测试，然后您写一点
production code to satisfy that test so
生产代码可以满足该测试
that the test goes green this is often
测试变绿这通常是
if you see people that are doing pair
如果您看到正在结伴的人
programming they call this ray
他们称这种射线为编程
Green refactoring you write somebody
绿色重构你写某人
writes the broken code the broken test
编写破损的代码破损的测试
and then somebody writes the green
然后有人写绿色
production code that makes the test go
使测试顺利进行的生产代码
green right and you ping-pong back and
绿色的权利，你乒乓球回来，
forth I write a broken unit test you
第四，我写了一个破碎的单元测试你
write some production code to fix the
编写一些生产代码以修复
unit test and then we keep going right
单元测试，然后我们继续正确
and often you don't want to write too
通常你也不想写
much test because you it'll break
很多测试，因为它会破坏
immediately if you write one more
如果您再写一封，请立即
assertion it'll break and so you write
断言会断，所以你写
just a little bit more production code
多一点生产代码
and now it's green and then green again
现在是绿色，然后又是绿色
then you go back and eventually you get
然后你回去，最终你得到
into this loop where you're constantly
进入这个循环，你不断
ping-ponging back and forth between
之间来回乒乓
production code and test code and this
生产代码和测试代码以及​​此
can seem very you know turbulent it's
看起来非常，你知道它是湍流的
like a bumpy airplane at first right it
像起初的颠簸飞机一样
can be it can be very confusing to work
可能会使工作非常混乱
this way because you're constantly
这样，因为你不断
moving back and forth between two pieces
在两块之间来回移动
of code but once you get used to it it
代码，但是一旦习惯了
can be very very very satisfying to work
可以非常非常满意地工作
this way and the reason is because you
这样，原因是因为你
end up doing several things by writing
最终通过写来做几件事
your tests first when you write your
在编写您的测试时首先要进行测试
tests first you write code that can be
首先测试您编写的代码可以
tested this is important right if you
测试这很重要，如果您
write code that is full of private
写满私人的代码
static classes then you're not gonna
静态类，那么你就不会
enjoy the process of testing that code
享受测试该代码的过程
it's gonna be very hard to test that
很难测试
code and so you won't do that because
代码，所以您不会这样做，因为
you know that you're gonna write the
你知道你要写
test that will test this thing so you're
测试会测试这个东西，所以你
not gonna do these things that make it
不会做这些事情
hard for you to get your work done and
很难让您完成工作，
when you write code that is testable
当您编写可测试的代码时
that is to say it's clean you're writing
就是说你写的很干净
code that has parts that are testable in
包含可测试部分的代码
isolation
隔离
isn't that true right a good
那不是真的好吗
object-oriented design is able to factor
面向对象的设计能够考虑
out the things that are invariant from
摆脱不变的事物
the things that are variant write in the
变种的东西写在
tests you have things that you want to
测试您是否有想要的东西
test and then the things that surround
测试，然后围绕的事物
it that are invariant you want to be
你想成为不变的
able to isolate in order to do that you
能够隔离以便做到这一点
need to be able to swap out parts of the
需要能够交换出部分
object graph you need to be able to
您需要具备的对象图
substitute parts of the autograph well
替换亲笔签名的部分
of course what what's a good way of
当然什么是好的方法
writing code that supports this goal of
编写支持该目标的代码
clean boundaries in the codebase
清除代码库中的边界
dependency injection right good clean
依赖注入权好干净
testable code is dependency injection
可测试的代码是依赖注入
friendly code and so these things have
友好的代码，所以这些东西都有
always been friends spring and testing
一直是春天和测试的朋友
have always been friends it's always
一直是朋友，一直都是
been a goal to make testing more
进行更多测试的目标
productive right with spring instead of
春季代替生产权
deploying this giant app server and then
部署这个巨大的应用服务器，然后
testing the code by running it in my EJB
通过在EJB中运行代码来测试代码
server or whatever you can just take a
服务器或任何你可以采取的
little pojo a regular java object and
小pojo一个常规的Java对象，
just poke at it in isolation so when you
只是孤立地戳它，所以当你
write tests first you write code that is
首先编写测试，然后编写代码
cleaner it's more object-oriented it's
更清洁，它更面向对象
more it has well-defined boundaries
更具有明确的界限
there's another benefit though forget
忘了还有另一个好处
about the technical stuff forget about
关于技术的东西忘了
architecture and code cleanliness
架构和代码清洁度
there's a much more important point here
还有一个更重要的一点
which is that it's very satisfying to
这是非常令人满意的
write your tests first and I mean at the
首先写你的测试，我的意思是
brain at the level of the of the
大脑的水平
chemicals in the brain it's satisfying
大脑中的化学物质令人满意
like I said human beings we are wired
就像我说的人类一样
our brains are wired up to recognize and
我们的大脑被连接起来以识别和
seek rewards related to achievement ok
寻求与成就相关的奖励
and so I'm sure some of you will
所以我敢肯定你们中的一些人会
appreciate this how many of you play
感谢你们有多少人在玩
video games ok right how many of you
好的，你们有多少电子游戏
just I mean I love the code so that's
我是说我喜欢代码，所以
one option how many of you just love to
一种选择，你们当中有多少人喜欢
code you go home and you and you do it
编码，您就可以回家了
in your own free time ok right what
在自己的空闲时间好吧
about exercise like jogging and running
关于慢跑和跑步等运动
and these K you know those kinds of
这些K你知道那种
things like ok so I'm gonna go ahead and
好的，所以我要继续
go on a limb here and I'm gonna go ahead
在这里走一走，我要继续
and say that people who said that they
并说那些说他们的人
love jogging are lying right nobody
慢跑爱说谎没有人
actually likes to jog they like to get
其实喜欢慢跑，他们喜欢得到
to the finish line right that's
到终点线那是
different I don't like to hurt instead I
不同，我不想伤害我
like to get to the finish line and go I
想去终点线然后走
did it right same thing for videogames
对电子游戏做了同样的事情吗
why do we why do people spend so much
为什么我们为什么人们花那么多钱
time sitting in from the video game or
坐在视频游戏中的时间，或者
programming right how many of you ever
进行编程，有多少人
sat down at like 9 o'clock on the in the
在9点钟坐下
morning and you're working on something
早上，你正在做某事
and you're making good progress and
并且您正在取得良好的进步，
you're working and you're working and
你在工作，你在工作，
you're working and the next thing you
你在工作，下一件事
know it's 6 o'clock at night or 9
知道现在是晚上六点或九点
o'clock or tomorrow right yeah I've had
还是明天或以后
days like that or days you know multiple
那样的日子或你认识多个日子
days right I'm sure how many of you have
好的日子，我确定你们有多少人
had something like that we just get lost
有这样的事情，我们迷路了
in time we call that getting into the
随着时间的流逝，我们称之为进入
zone right it's a very important aspect
正确的区域是一个非常重要的方面
of what we're trying to do here you get
我们在这里尝试做的事情
into the zone and the reason we get into
进入区域以及我们进入的原因
the zone with code and with jogging and
带有代码和慢跑的区域，以及
with video games is because these if
电子游戏是因为这些
we're doing it correctly
我们做得正确
we achieve flow we achieve the state of
我们达到流程，达到状态
having constant small horizons to which
有一个恒定的小视野
were making
在做
slow but steady progress if we make
如果我们能取得缓慢而稳定的进步
progress towards our horizon we feel
我们感到向着地平线前进
like we're making we're moving somewhere
就像我们要移动到某个地方
and our brain loves that it desires that
我们的大脑喜欢它渴望的
so when you used when you do test-driven
所以当您使用测试驱动程序时
development you're optimizing for that
您正在为此优化的开发
dopamine hit that feeling in the brain
多巴胺打击大脑的那种感觉
that says oh this is awesome right you
说哦，这太棒了
get towards when you get a green test
当你通过绿色测试时
its feedback it feels like you're
它的反馈感觉就像你在
getting somewhere and that's awesome
到达某个地方，那太棒了
because if you have a green test and
因为如果您进行绿色测试，
you're doing test-driven development you
您正在进行测试驱动的开发
have a green test it also means you've
进行绿色测试也意味着您已经
shipped the software you've got software
附带了您拥有的软件
that's working right compare that to the
这是正确的比较
other way the other way around is you
反之亦然
write the code first and then you write
先写代码，然后再写
the test well if I've got the code
如果我有代码，则测试良好
working the first time it works it's
第一次工作就可以了
great right it's like oh it's awesome my
太好了，这就像哦，太棒了
code works but now I have to go write
代码有效，但现在我必须去写
the test it's a chore
测试是一件琐事
right I gotta uh I've gotta go write
对，我要去写
documentation uh maybe I'll do that next
文档，也许我接下来会做
time you know and and that's the other
你知道的时间，那是另一个
thing is you you feel like well it's not
事情是你，你感觉很好，不是
that important it's already working in
重要的是它已经在
my machine right we've all said those
我的机器对，我们都说过
famous last words and so if you have the
著名的遗言，所以如果您有
discipline to write the test first you
纪律要先写测试
won't get into that situation you'll
不会陷入那种情况，你会
write cleaner code your write code that
写更干净的代码
has tests and it's you know you can you
有测试，这是你知道的你可以
can do things as a result of those tests
那些测试可以做的事情
you can take you can have confidence in
你可以带你有信心
the results of those tests you'll have
这些测试的结果
the dopamine hit like I said and so and
就像我说的那样，多巴胺受到打击等等
you'll be able to move faster at least
您至少可以更快地移动
it'll feel faster so all these reasons
感觉会更快，所以所有这些原因
all these reasons I think are important
我认为所有这些原因都很重要
when considering test-driven development
在考虑测试驱动的开发时
okay so we're gonna write tests just a
好吧，我们要编写测试只是
lot of tests today we're gonna write
今天我们要写很多测试
code using spring of course I'm we're
使用spring的代码，当然我是
gonna do so of course at my second
我第二次当然要这么做
favorite place on the Internet
互联网上最喜欢的地方
start that spring today oh this is my
今天春天开始，哦，这是我的
second favorite place on the Internet of
互联网上第二受欢迎的地方
course as always after production
生产后一如既往
I love production you should love
我爱你应该爱的作品
production you should go is early and
你应该去的生产是早
often as possible
经常
bring the kids bring the family the
带孩子带家人
weather is amazing it's the happiest
天气太神奇了，这是最快乐的一天
place on earth it's better than Euro
地球上比欧元还好
Disney but if you haven't been to
迪士尼，但如果您没有去过
production you can begin your journey
生产即可开始您的旅程
here at start
开始这里
that's spring that IO if you need
如果需要的话，那就是春天
inspiration there early morning before a
灵感来自清晨
cup of tea or coffee start that spring
那个春天开始喝杯茶或咖啡
that IO
那个IO
if your children are restless and they
如果你的孩子们躁动不安，他们
cannot sleep start that spring that IO
无法入睡的那个春天开始
and if you suffer from indigestion after
如果你以后消化不良
a long night of alcohol abuse and PHP
一整夜的酗酒和PHP
start that spring that I oh alright so
从那个春天开始，我哦，好吧
we're gonna build a new application
我们将建立一个新的应用程序
we're gonna call this the producer and
我们将其称为生产者，
we're just gonna bring in some reactive
我们只会带来一些反应
stuff so I'm gonna be I think most of
的东西，所以我想我大部分
you should be at this point familiar
在这一点上你应该很熟悉
with some of the reactive support and
有一些反应性的支持和
spring we're gonna create a reactive
春天，我们要创造一个反应
application a web application that talks
应用程序，一个Web应用程序
to a reactive MongoDB database I'm gonna
到反应性的MongoDB数据库
use the spring cut contract verifier
使用Spring 切割合同验证器
okay so just a bunch of stuff here
好吧，这里只是一堆东西
we're gonna hit generate and I'm gonna
我们要点击generate，我要
open this project up in my downloads
在我的下载中打开此项目
directory so ueo producer there we go
目录，所以ueo生产者在那里
and that's gonna open up IntelliJ it
这将打开IntelliJ
doesn't matter what you use what tooling
不管您使用什么工具
use I'm gonna use IntelliJ I like
使用我要使用我喜欢的IntelliJ
intelligent but anything that supports
聪明，但任何支持
Java 8 or greater will work just fine in
Java 8或更高版本可以在
this case and we're gonna build an
这种情况下，我们将建立一个
application starting with the tests as
从测试开始的应用程序
always so let's close this out that's
总是这样，让我们​​结束这就是
the wrong project goodbye to you alright
错误的项目告别你
now the goal here is just a right now
现在这里的目标只是现在
application that writes data to the
将数据写入到的应用程序
database so the first thing that we're
数据库，所以我们要做的第一件事
gonna do is ignore the production code
要做的就是忽略生产代码
and go straight to the test you notice
并直接进行测试，您会注意到
that when you use a spring boot and the
当您使用 spring boot 和
spring initializer you get a sort of
春天的初始化，你得到一种
empty stub of a test and that's an
测试的空存根，这是一个
interesting kind of like it's nice it's
有趣的是，它很好
a reminder that we should be doing
提醒我们应该做的
certain things but if I'm honest I never
某些事情，但老实说，我永远不会
keep this test I always just throw this
保持这个测试，我总是只丢这个
away right I want to start a different
马上我想开始一个不同的
way so that's the first thing but it's
方式，这是第一件事，但这是
nice that we have that and it's
很高兴我们有那个
important to know that we do have that
重要的是要知道我们确实有
the reason we had that is because when
我们之所以拥有那是因为
you generate new projects on the
您在
initializer you've got test support
具有测试支持的初始值设定项
build into the dependencies there's no
建立依赖关系没有
checkbox I didn't have to choose that
复选框，我不必选择
before it's just assumed in 2019 that
在2019年之前假设
you're going to write tests right
您将正确编写测试
there's no way to opt out of that so we
没有办法选择退出，所以我们
have that by default so now I want to
有默认情况下，所以现在我想
write a test and the first thing I'm
写测试，我第一件事
gonna do since we know that I'm gonna
会做，因为我们知道我会
write data to the database is I'm gonna
将数据写入数据库
use I'm gonna create an entity or an
使用我要创建一个实体或
object now there's two different
现在有两个不同的对象
discussions there's two different trains
讨论有两种不同的火车
of thoughts here about how you should do
关于您应该如何做的想法
testing should you do inside out where
测试你应该从内到外做
you write tests for the smallest thing
你为最小的事情写测试
in the system and then work your way out
在系统中，然后解决问题
to the biggest thing so from the basic
从基本到最大
object all the way to the service or the
一直反对服务或
user interface right that's inside out
内在的用户界面权限
or should you go outside in where you
还是应该去外面的地方
talk when you work from the outside the
当你从外面工作时说话
the interface the user interface or the
界面，用户界面或
REST API
REST API
and then start writing code inwards
然后开始向内编写代码
writing the small stuff inwards and
向内写一些小东西，
there's two different ways to think
有两种不同的思考方式
about it if you start from the inside
如果你从内部开始
from the bottom if you think about it
从底部开始，如果您考虑一下
the more specific thing if you work at
更具体的事情，如果你在
the smallest level and then start
最小的水平然后开始
testing outward then you can have
向外测试，那么你可以
different teams working on things right
不同的团队在正确地工作
different teams can start on different
不同的团队可以从不同的角度出发
services and they can start at the
服务，他们可以从
bottom and they can work in parallel so
底部，他们可以并行工作，所以
that's good for maybe maybe that's
这可能对那很有好处
better for larger teams on the other
更适合较大的团队
hand if you know that your system has a
如果您知道您的系统有一个
lot of risk in the integration layer
集成层存在很大风险
then it might be more valuable for you
那对你来说可能更有价值
to start outside in because that's where
从外面开始，因为那是
the risk is that's what you want to get
风险就是你想要得到的
that's what you want to be sure about
那就是你要确定的
right so you can there's a it's like a
对，所以你可以有一个像
whole it's just one of those things it's
整体而言，这只是其中之一
like tabs versus spaces and by the way
像制表符与空格之类的方式
the answer is of course spaces but
答案当然是空格，但是
anyway
无论如何
it's like tabs for versus spaces you can
这就像您可以使用空格的制表符
have it a whole long discussion about
有一个完整的长期讨论
this and there's good reasons for both
这和两者都有充分的理由
sides I don't care ok I'm just gonna I'm
双方，我不在乎，好吧，我要
gonna start inside out only because it
会因为它而从内而外开始
allows me to demonstrate certain things
让我演示某些事情
in a natural order at least natural for
以自然顺序至少
me ok so first things first I want to
我好，所以首先要先
create an entity and I'm gonna persist
创建一个实体，我要坚持下去
in the database it's gonna be called a
在数据库中将其称为
reservation and so I'm gonna create an
保留，所以我要创建一个
object just to demonstrate that that
只是为了证明那个
object is valid within itself so I'm
对象在自身内部有效，所以我
gonna create a simple test like this
会创建一个像这样的简单测试
public void create ok so here we go
公共无效创建，所以我们开始
throw those exceptions whoa not editor
抛出那些不是编辑者的异常
kit whatever that is here we go and it's
随便装什么，我们去
just gonna be the objects so I'm going
只是成为对象所以我要去
to say reservation R equals new
说保留R等于新
reservation and you can see that we've
预订，您可以看到我们已经
got no entity
没有实体
we've got no type so I'm gonna hit
我们没有类型，所以我要打
create class I've got my production code
创建类我有我的生产代码
good the test is green again so to speak
好，测试又是绿色的，可以这么说
if you have a compiler error that's a
如果您遇到编译器错误
failing test okay it's red it counts as
测试失败，是红色，算作是
a failing test now I want to create an
现在测试失败了，我想创建一个
object with valid States I'm going to
具有有效状态的对象，我要去
create a constructor that takes an ID in
创建一个接受ID的构造函数
a parameter so I'll go back to my
一个参数，所以我将回到我的
production code and create that there
生产代码并在那里创建
now I could create the constructor but I
现在我可以创建构造函数，但是我
prefer to use a Lombok alright so I'm
我宁愿使用龙目岛，所以我
just gonna do this and there we go
只是要这样做，然后我们去
there's my my constructor etc now I go
现在有我的构造函数，等等，我去
back to here now I want to prove that
回到现在，我想证明
this is gonna work I'm gonna say assert
这会工作，我要说断言
equals you know re get name
等于你知道重新命名
and I want to say Jane okay now what if
我想说简好吧，如果
I run this test you think that's gonna
我进行了这项测试，您认为那会
work I expect it will probably work all
我希望它可能会全部工作
I'm proving is that if I put something
我证明的是，如果我放点东西
in the constructor I can get it back out
在构造函数中，我可以将其取回
now this is one way to test things you
现在，这是测试您事物的一种方法
know about J in and of course another
在J中当然知道J
thing I could do is if I have a more
我可以做的是，如果我还有更多
complex test I can use a matcher
复杂的测试，我可以使用匹配器
I can say let's use a matcher and
我可以说让我们使用匹配器
matress dot you know equals ignoring
你知道的床垫点等于忽略
case Jane okay that's a very simple
情况简好，这很简单
thing to express I can also create my
表达的东西我也可以创造我的
own mattress this is where this is this
自己的床垫，这是这里
is one of the nice things about this is
这是一件好事
I can create my own matcher but the
我可以创建自己的匹配器，但是
thing is you've got to be careful it's
事情是你必须要小心
very tempting because the type that is
非常诱人，因为那是
expected here is a matcher and mattre is
应该在这里是一个匹配器，而遮罩是
an interface it's very tempting to say
一个非常诱人的界面
well I'll just create my own matcher you
好吧，我将创建一个自己的匹配器
know it's gonna happen if you create
知道如果您创建它将会发生
your own metro since you didn't read the
你自己没读过地铁
documentation
文件资料
it it's a I think they're trying to
我认为他们正在尝试
communicate I think they're trying to
沟通，我认为他们正在努力
tell us something so so don't do don't
告诉我们一些事情，所以不要这样做
do that very clearly okay so instead you
这样做很清楚，所以您
get a new bass masher and the bass
得到一个新的低音捣碎器和低音
matcher just it's just a very simple
匹配器只是一个非常简单的
interface and you know you may not have
界面，您知道您可能没有
to do this okay that's fine
做到这一点就可以了
there's a bass matcher and the idea is
有一个低音匹配器，想法是
that you say okay given an object of
你说好的，给定一个对象
type object I'm gonna say item dot you
输入对象，我要说出一个点
know string whoops
知道弦乐
string item dot care at 0 equals or
字符串项点护理为0等于或
better yet we can do is upper case there
更好的是，我们可以做的是大写
we go
我们去
character is upper case so I'm saying
字符是大写，所以我说
given a string the first name the name
给字符串一个名字，名字
should be upper case okay and if there's
应该是大写的，如果有的话
an error now I have a place to you know
现在有一个错误我有一个地方你知道
the the name should be valid upper case
名称应为大写字母
and I should have written some business
我应该写点生意
logic here to enforce that but you get
强制执行此逻辑，但您得到
the idea right now I can describe a
现在我可以描述一个想法
complex thing and the better part is I
复杂的事情，更好的是我
can actually extract this out into a
实际上可以将其提取到
separate class and other people who have
单独的班级和其他拥有
the same test scenario can reuse this
相同的测试场景可以重用
rather than re-encoding this every
而不是每次都重新编码
single time we want to write a test
我们想写一次测试
so very simple example here we go run
非常简单的例子，我们开始运行
and now the message is also built-in
现在消息也是内置的
okay good stuff okay now another thing
好东西好吧现在好了
is you can use a search a I like assert
你可以使用搜索我喜欢断言
J so here I say assert shouldn't true
J所以我在这里说断言不应该是真的
are e dot get name and I get assert true
e点得到名称，而我断言为真
asserted that thank you sir cert that
断言，谢谢您，先生
that
那
or not search
还是不搜索
[Music]
[音乐]
sergej that gee-whiz is equal to
谢尔吉，gee-whiz等于
ignoring case Jane okay so now I get
忽略简，好吧，现在我明白了
this nice type save completions so a lot
这种不错的类型可以节省完成次数
of you get all this stuff for free on
你们这些人免费获得所有这些东西
the classpath already off the bat we've
类路径已经不可行了
got some basic stuff that we can use now
有一些基本的东西，我们现在可以使用
the next thing that I want to test is my
接下来要测试的是我的
ability to persist this objects into the
将该对象持久化到
database so I'm gonna create a
数据库，所以我要创建一个
reservation entity test I'm going to
我要去预订实体测试
persist this object into MongoDB in
将对象持久保存到MongoDB中
order to persist that I'm gonna I'm
为了坚持下去，我要
gonna prove that the mapping is correct
会证明映射是正确的
okay so I'm going to create an entity
好吧，我要创建一个实体
test to prove that and I'll create a
测试以证明这一点，我将创建一个
reservation I'll say reservation R
保留我会说保留R
equals new reservation and I'll pass a
等于新的保留，我将通过
null for the ID and then Jane for the
ID为null，然后Jane为
name and I want to prove that I can talk
名字，我想证明我可以说话
to MongoDB so I'm going to inject a auto
到MongoDB，所以我要注入一个自动
wired reactive MongoDB template okay
有线反应式MongoDB模板还可以
and I'm I didn't write them on go to
而且我没有去写他们
template I know that that works it's a
模板，我知道那是可行的
layer below now the thing is I need to
现在下面的东西是我需要
get this from somewhere and spring
从某个地方得到这个春天
already knows how to create it so I
已经知道如何创建它，所以我
could bring in spring but I don't want
可以带来春天，但我不想
to test I don't want to launch all of my
测试我不想启动所有我的
spring application just to have that
春季申请只是为了
instead I'm gonna use a test slice I'll
相反，我将使用测试切片
say let's use a spring render to launch
说让我们使用Spring 渲染启动
this with spring and then I'm gonna use
春天来了，然后我会用
data Mongo test so this is gonna tell
数据Mongo测试，所以这可以告诉我们
spring hey spring don't bother using all
春天嘿春天不要打扰所有
the auto configuration just use the auto
自动配置只需使用自动
configuration related to the stuff in
与中的东西相关的配置
the database right so MongoDB in this
数据库对，所以MongoDB在这
case Andy will do a great job talking
案例安迪说话会做得很好
about this kind of stuff that test
关于这种测试的东西
slices in great detail later but what we
稍后会详细介绍，但我们
need to know is I'm going to say
需要知道的是我要说的是
template dot save reservation and that's
模板点保存预订，这就是
gonna give me a result now in reactive
现在要给我反应的结果
programming you're given these things
编程给你这些东西
called publishers mano is a kind of
叫做发布者mano是一种
publisher publishers are asynchronous
发布者发布者是异步的
okay so testing becomes very difficult
好的，所以测试变得非常困难
when you do asynchronous reactive data
当您执行异步反应数据时
because you don't have the data you have
因为你没有数据
a promise that the data will come
保证数据将到来
eventually and so there's a nice
最终，所以有一个不错的
abstraction a nice API in reactor which
在反应堆中抽象一个不错的API
is our reactive API to allow us to poke
是我们的反应式API，可让我们戳
at or assert things about the results so
对结果持肯定态度
here I can say given this publisher
在这里我可以说给这个出版商
let's assert that the reservation that
让我们断言保留
comes back has a name that's equal to
回来的名字等于
Jane and let's assert that the ID is not
简，让我们断言ID不是
know right so we sent to no but when it
知道是正确的，所以我们发送给no，但是当它
comes back from the database it should
从数据库返回它应该
be not know
不知道
alright so there's the reactive testing
好了，所以有反应性测试
mechanism there okay so let's see if
那里的机制好吧，让我们看看
that works
这样可行
now this is we think I think this is
现在这是我们认为我认为这是
probably gonna work right if I had done
如果我做了，可能会工作正常
something different maybe I had named my
有些不同，也许我已经命名了我的
entity differently you know for example
例如，您知道的实体不同
this if this wasn't named ID
如果未命名为ID
Mikey then I would have had to have a
Mikey然后我不得不
tie Dean I want to make sure that that
绑院长，我要确保
works correctly right but by convention
正确工作，但按照惯例
that key the the field named ideas named
那个关键的领域命名思想命名
correctly and also if I have a different
正确地，如果我有不同的话
document you know I could do something
证明你知道我可以做点什么
here where I could actually look at the
在这里我实际上可以看
annotation and see if that's working
注释，看看是否有效
correctly so that worked MongoDB is
正确地工作MongoDB是
clearly working and it's fast now what
显然工作正常，现在速度很快
about a custom query right queries are
关于自定义查询权限的查询是
strings there's something you want to
字符串，你想做些什么
test so I'm going to test my repository
测试，所以我要测试我的存储库
I'm going to create a repository but I'm
我要创建一个存储库，但是
not gonna I don't have to test my
我不用去测试我的
repository my most of my repository will
我大部分的资料库都会
work just fine right that's the spring
工作就好了，那是春天
data team does a great job with testing
数据团队在测试方面做得很好
the implementations for the repositories
存储库的实现
the only time you really need to test it
真正需要测试的唯一时间
is when you're using a custom query so
是当您使用自定义查询时
I'm gonna inject my reservation
我要注入我的预订
repository here okay and I don't have
仓库在这里好吧，我没有
that yeah that's production code so
是的，这是生产代码，所以
we'll create that and it's just gonna be
我们将创建它，它将成为
an interface so interface extends
接口，以便接口扩展
reactive crud repository managing
反应堆存储库管理
reservations there you go okay and I
那里的预订你还可以，我
want to create a custom query that says
想要创建一个自定义查询，说
given a request for all the reservations
要求所有保留
by name where the name equals name
按名称，其中名称等于名称
returned those results it's gonna return
返回了那些结果，它将返回
a reactive stream that contains all the
包含所有
reservations whose reservation name
其预订名称的预订
property equals name so there's my
属性等于名称，所以有我的
repository and I want to prove that that
资料库，我想证明
works so what I'm gonna do is I'm going
工作，所以我要做的就是我要去
to insert I'm gonna delete everything in
插入我要删除的所有内容
the database I'm going to write four
该数据库我要写四个
records then I'm going to query by name
记录，然后我要按名称查询
okay and assert count so that's my logic
好吧，断言计数，这就是我的逻辑
here so I'm gonna say flux not just a b
在这里，我要说的是通量，而不仅仅是ab
c c dot map name equals new reservation
cc点图名称等于新的保留
passing a null passing in that and what
传递一个null传递那个和什么
a flat map that i'm gonna save each are
我要保存的平面地图是
into the database like this passing in
像这样传入数据库
there and when that happens I'm gonna
在那里，那时候我要去
say find all the
说找到所有
in the database that matches this string
在数据库中与此字符串匹配
and before I do that I want to say this
在我这样做之前，我想说这个
not repository don't delete all and then
不是存储库，不要全部删除，然后
many okay so I'm stringing together
好多，所以我要在一起
these reactive streams here I'm using
这些我正在使用的反应流
the operators in reactor to do that so
反应堆中的操作员这样做
there we go there's my my reactive
那我们去那是我的反应
stream and I want to poke at that result
流，我想戳一下结果
I'm going to say step verifier that
我要说的是步骤验证器
create reservation flux expect next
创建预留流量期望下一个
count equals two right I should have two
伯爵等于二我应该有两个
results that are of type C or name C so
类型为C或名称为C的结果
let's run this code and see what we get
让我们运行这段代码，看看我们得到了什么
all right seems to be okay sometimes
有时候似乎还可以
though just to be healthy just to be
虽然只是为了健康
sure it's always good to ask yourself is
确保问自己总是好事
my test broken right and as a result am
我的测试不正确，结果是
I getting the wrong results so sometimes
我得到了错误的结果，所以有时
you can just test the negative you you
你可以测试负面的你
break the tests so that it should show a
打破测试，以便它应该显示一个
failure just so that you know that
失败只是让你知道
everything is working right sometimes I
一切正常，有时候我
write so many tests and it always just
写这么多测试，它总是
works I'm like that can't be right I
作品我觉得那是不对的
can't be that good right
不能那么好吧
no way so it's always good just
没办法，所以总是很好
especially late at night always break
特别是深夜总是休息
the test to make sure you're not doing
测试以确保您没有做
something crazy that's that's masking a
疯狂的东西掩盖了
real problem
真正的问题
so that broke which is what we expect
所以这就是我们期望的
okay so we're gonna put it back to two
好吧，我们要放回两个
and we know things fine now I want to
而且我们知道现在情况很好，我想
move up one more layer I'm going to
再向上移动一层
create an at reservation HTTP API okay
创建一个保留HTTP API可以
reservation HTTP test and this is gonna
保留HTTP测试，这将
be something that's gonna test the web
成为可以测试网络的东西
tier so I'm gonna say query or no get
层，所以我要说查询还是没有得到
all reservations okay like so there's
所有的预订都可以，所以
that okay and I'm gonna use run with but
没关系，我要使用run with但
I'm gonna be testing their whipped here
我要在这里测试他们的鞭打
not the data tier right I don't want to
不是我不想要的数据层
test the MongoDB stuff we already did
测试我们已经做过的MongoDB东西
that that's already working so instead
那已经在工作，所以
I'm gonna use a web slice and this slice
我要用一个网片和这个片
is gonna activate the stuff related to
会激活与
the web tier and in order to test my
网络层并为了测试我的
reactive HTTP API I'm gonna inject the
反应性的HTTP API，我要注入
web test client okay and here this is
网络测试客户端可以，这是
going to make a get call to reservations
打电话预约
and I'm going to expect the data to come
我期望数据会到来
back I'm going to expect that the status
返回我会期待状态
is a HTTP 200 and expect that the body
是HTTP 200，并且希望该正文
or that the headers has a content
或者标题包含内容
type that's compatible with media type
与媒体类型兼容的类型
application JSON and I'm gonna expect
应用程序JSON，我期待
that the body has a JSON path so how
该主体具有JSON路径，如何
many of you know JSON path
你们很多人都知道JSON路径
Jason path is like a query language for
Jason路径就像是一种查询语言
drilling down into the document
深入文档
structure of a JSON object like exit
JSON对象（如exit）的结构
XPath from years ago okay so is equal to
XPath从几年前还可以，所以等于
Jane all right so I'm gonna say when the
简好吧，我要说的是
first result comes back I'm expecting
我期待第一个结果回来
that first result to be have a name
第一个结果是要有一个名字
equal to Jane and I'll have the second
等于简，我有第二个
one equal to Jo okay so there we go
一个等于Jo好的，所以我们走了
there's my two records and that's my my
有我的两个记录，那是我的
simple test and now of course what's
简单的测试，现在当然是什么
wrong with this code first of all is
这段代码首先是错误的
that gonna work of course not I haven't
当然可以，但不是
written any production code yet so let's
编写任何生产代码，所以让我们
do that I can see already there's one
这样做我可以看到已经有一个
important piece okay okay so this is a
重要的部分好吧好吧这是一个
configuration class great and I'm gonna
配置类很棒，我要
use a functional reactive endpoint here
在此处使用功能性反应性端点
I'll say server response and the server
我会说服务器响应和服务器
response is just gonna produce a simple
反应只会产生一个简单的
come on it's trying to tell me to use
来吧，它试图告诉我使用
Kotlin did you see that
Kotlin你看到了吗
those were Kotlin types so route dot
这些是Kotlin类型的，所以路线点
build I'm gonna say get forward slash
建立我要说向前斜线
reservations new handler function okay
保留新的处理程序功能
so my job is going to be to inject the
所以我的工作将是注入
reservation repository here are our I'll
预订库，这是我们的工作
say server response that okay that body
说服务器响应没问题，
RR that find all reservation class ok so
找到所有预订舱位的RR如此
there's that replace it with a lambda
有一个用lambda替换它
static imports very simple HTTP endpoint
静态导入非常简单的HTTP端点
right not a big deal now I want to test
没什么大不了的，我现在要测试
this in order to test it of course I
为了测试它，我当然
need to bring in the config class so I'm
需要引入配置类，所以我
going to use the the value and it'll be
将使用该值，它将是
reservation HTTP test etc is that gonna
保留HTTP测试等
work no of course not there's a couple
工作当然没有，有一对
of obvious reasons first of all did did
首先有明显的原因
you see me create two records with Jane
你看到我和简一起创造了两条记录
and Joe in it no and even if I did it
和乔在里面，即使我做到了
doesn't look like we even got that far
看起来我们甚至还没走得那么远
does it look at this well first of all
首先看得好吗
it says 404 not found that's a totally
它说404找不到那是完全
different issue
不同的问题
what do you want me to do this I think
我想你想让我做什么
it wants me to do that let's try that
它希望我这样做，让我们尝试一下
yep okay so that didn't work
是的，所以那没用
import it's already present well
导入它已经存在
value is equal to that oh it's
值等于那个哦
reservation HTTP config ha HTTP or did I
保留HTTP配置ha HTTP还是我
even call it reservation I wrote the
甚至称它为保留，我写了
production code I called it test
我称之为测试的生产代码
I've got tests on the brain friends oh
我已经对大脑朋友进行了测试哦
that's so confusing okay so here we go
太令人困惑了，所以我们开始
configuration names matter good stuff
配置名称很重要
okay it's all and think about is how I'm
好吧，这就是我的想法
gonna test this code okay
要测试这段代码好吗
so let's try that again this time with
所以这次让我们再试一次
less can feel it's did I just oh no no
很少有人能感觉到我只是哦，不，不
it's configuration yeah yeah all right
是配置，是的，好的
HP config very good okay this time with
惠普配置很好，这次可以
more gusto come on
更多的热情
no runnable methods fine you're confused
没有可运行的方法，您很困惑
I get it
我知道了
reservation it should be test how are we
保留，应该测试我们怎么样
doing okay so there we go we're
做得很好，所以我们去了
requiring a beating of type reservation
需要击败类型保留
repository so again because it's a web
再次如此，因为它是一个网络
slice because it's using the web flex
切片，因为它使用的是Web Flex
slice the stuff in the database layer it
在数据库层中切东西
doesn't exist it's not it doesn't get
不存在不是不是没有
created so I need to inject I need to
创建，所以我需要注入我需要
create a mock version of the repository
创建版本库的模拟版本
like that now I could create my own
这样我现在可以创建自己的
implementation you know that kind of
实现，你知道那种
thing but that would be a lot of work so
东西，但这将是很多工作，所以
what I would like to do is to use
我想做的是使用
mockito I would mock out the object now
我现在要模拟对象
I have spring spring knows about all the
我有春天，春天知道所有
objects I want spring to use a mock
我想让Spring使用模拟对象
object and replace the thing that I want
反对并替换我想要的东西
with that mock so that'll be fine and I
用那个模拟游戏，这样就可以了，我
can do mock bean okay mock bean tells
可以做模拟 bean 好吗模拟 bean 告诉
spring find this object in the
春天在
application context if it exists and
应用程序上下文（如果存在）以及
create a mock version of it if it if it
创建一个模拟版本（如果有）
if it exists replace the one that's
如果存在，请替换
already there if it exists and if it
已经存在，如果存在，是否存在
doesn't exist then add this mockito mock
不存在，然后添加此模仿
version of it and because it's a Makita
版本，因为它是牧田
mock remember a mock is just an object
模拟记住，模拟只是一个对象
that has empty you know default values
有空，你知道默认值
no false 0 etc right
没有错误的0等
but what I want is not a mock what I
但是我想要的不是嘲笑我
want is a stub a stub is a mock with
想要是一个存根，一个存根是一个模拟
some pre-programmed values with
一些预先设定的值
pre-programmed behavior so I'm gonna say
预先设定的行为，所以我要说
mockito dot when this dot repository to
当这个点存储库到
find all then return flux dot just new
找到所有然后返回的磁通点只是新的
reservation one Jane to what did I say
对我说的话保留一位简
Jo okay there's my pre-programmed
好的，我已经预先设定好了
results okay and let's see if that works
结果还好，让我们看看是否可行
looks good okay so that's good now I
看起来很好，所以现在很好
want to build a client I'm gonna go back
想建立一个客户，我要回去
here actually I'll just go ahead and get
实际上我会继续前进
rid of some of this stuff I don't need
摆脱一些我不需要的东西
MongoDB don't need this I do want a
MongoDB不需要这个，我想要一个
consumer and I want the verifier okay
消费者，我希望验证者可以
let's do burn or rather okay so I hit
让我们燃烧或好吧，所以我打
generate and what I want to do now is I
生成，我现在想做的是
want to build a consumer to talk to that
想要建立一个与之对话的消费者
API and so what I'm gonna do is I'm
API，所以我要做的就是
going to open up this application in my
打算在我的电脑上打开这个应用程序
IDE consumer okay I'll go to my code and
IDE使用者，好的，我去看一下代码
the consumer side I'm gonna create a
消费者方面，我将创建一个
micro service you know client basically
您基本了解客户的微服务
something that people who want to use
人们想要使用的东西
this can use to talk to my API so I'll
这可以用来和我的API通讯，所以我会
say reservation client test and the
说预订客户测试和
production cut in the end the test code
量产到底测试代码
and it'll be run with spring run or
它将以春季运行或
class it'll be a spring boot test and
上课，这将是一个 spring boot 测试，
what I'm gonna do is I'm going to make a
我要去做的是
call to my micro service I'm gonna
打电话给我的微服务
provide a client that people can use to
提供人们可以使用的客户
make calls to the micro service I'm
拨打我正在使用的微服务
gonna consume that micro service so in
会消耗微服务，所以在
order to do that I'll inject a reference
为了做到这一点，我将注入参考
to my reservation client which of course
给我的预订客户
we haven't written yet halfway so here
我们还没有写一半，所以在这里
we are
我们是
and I'll add the client code there and
我将在其中添加客户端代码，
this is going to be a spring bean of
这将是
course and it'll have an endpoint you
当然会有终点
know like this so we you know we can see
知道这样，所以我们知道
what we're gonna do here so this don't
我们在这里要做什么，所以不要
client thought get all reservations and
客户的想法得到所有保留和
it'll be a publisher of reservation res
它将成为保留资源的发布者
equals that and obviously I need this
等于那个，显然我需要这个
type on the class path so I'll create
在类路径上输入内容，以便我创建
this class here this production code
这个班这个生产代码
it's a DTO right so
这是DTO，所以
and ID and I want at data at all arcs
和ID，我想获取所有弧线处的数据
constructor at norc's constructor and I
我和norc的构造函数的构造函数
want this method okay so there we go in
希望这种方法可以，所以我们进入
order to create that I'm going to use
为了创建我将要使用的
the reactive web clients I'm gonna
我要使用的反应式网络客户端
inject that I could create a constructor
注入我可以创建一个构造函数
but I like Lombok Lombok it makes it
但是我喜欢龙目岛龙目岛
easy so I can just inject it by a via
容易，所以我可以通过一个通路注入
constructor which gets written for me
为我写的构造函数
I'll say this client get dot URI HTTP
我会说这个客户端得到点URI HTTP
localhost 8080 forward slash
本地主机8080正斜杠
reservations that retrieved that body to
保留检索到该机构
explore Ezzor vation doc class there we
探索Ezzor vation doc类，我们
go
走
simple right now in my test code I want
现在在我想要的测试代码中很简单
to prove I want to assert things about
证明我想断言有关
the data I'll say when the data comes
数据到时我会说的数据
back I want to let's say that I look at
返回我想说我看着
the data I'm gonna use a predicate here
我将在此处使用谓词的数据
I'll use this predicate that we you know
我将使用这个谓词，我们知道
you can imagine writing yourself it's
你可以想象自己写的是
very simple so I'm gonna say a list of
非常简单，我要说一个清单
string names equals arrays dot as list
字符串名称等于数组点作为列表
Jane and Joe okay so there's my list and
简和乔好吧，这是我的清单，
I'm gonna say when the data comes in
我要说数据何时输入
reservation get name I'm gonna say names
保留名字我要说名字
dot contains this so it should be one of
点包含此内容，因此应为以下内容之一
those valid names verify complete okay
那些有效的名字验证完全可以
very simple and I'm gonna I have to do
非常简单，我要去做
this twice because there's two different
这两次，因为有两个不同
results they're gonna come back each of
结果他们要回来的每个
which will match one of these names so
这将与这些名称之一匹配，因此
now let's see if I run this code have I
现在让我们看看我是否运行此代码
done everything I need to do I think
我做了我想做的一切
we're gonna it's gonna fail but I don't
我们会失败的，但我不会
know why why I have an idea why but I
知道为什么为什么我有一个想法为什么但是我
still don't know why I let's see what
还是不知道为什么我让我们看看
happens if it's fails okay
如果失败会发生
first failure okay reservation client
第一次失败好预订客户端
needs a beam of type web client fair
需要一类类型的网络客户公平
enough so I'm going to factory a beam of
够了，所以我要出厂一束
the reactive web client all right web
响应式Web客户端可以访问Web
client and I'm gonna inject the web
客户，我要注入网络
client builder because spring will pre
客户构建者，因为春季将
configure that with anything I want it
用我想要的任何东西进行配置
to configure like security and
配置安全性和
client-side load balancing and all that
客户端负载平衡等
kind of stuff and then I just provide
种东西，然后我只提供
the fine I just call build and get the
好的，我只是打电话给build并且得到
final resulting thing now what's gonna
最后的结果现在会怎样
happen let's see what happens if we run
发生，让我们看看如果我们跑步
this test one more time
这个测试再一次
Oh uh-oh we've got a problem don't we
哦，哦，我们有问题吗
Jabba net connection exception it's
Jabba网络连接异常是
tried to call that service but of course
试图致电该服务，但当然
the service isn't running this is a bit
服务没有运行，这有点
of a problem isn't it
是不是有问题
we've moved to micro services I've got
我们已经转向了我拥有的微服务
producer and consumer client and service
生产者，消费者客户和服务
and now one is calling the other over
现在一个正在呼叫另一个
the network I don't I don't have that
网络，我没有，我没有
service running now I don't know I'm
服务正在运行，我不知道我在
here we're here in Europe and and Europe
在这里，我们在欧洲和欧洲
things are a little different than where
事情和哪里有些不同
I'm from I I live in San Francisco and
我来自旧金山的II
the Bay Area in the States
美国湾区
it's okay in in in San Francisco though
虽然在旧金山还可以
a very friendly polite greeting for
一个非常友好的礼貌问候
somebody who comes to work with your
来和你一起工作的人
organization in your organization as a
组织中的组织
new employee a very polite thing to say
新员工有礼貌的话
to them is hello or welcome or please
向他们问好或欢迎或请
you know have a seat here join us you
你知道这里有位子加入我们吧
know that's a very welcoming inclusive
知道这是一个非常欢迎的包容性
thing to say it's very polite a very
很有礼貌
vulgar thing very very vulgar okay one
庸俗的东西，非常非常庸俗，好一个
of the things that you can say that
你可以说的话
people sometimes do and it's very I've
人们有时候会做，这是我非常
seen people leave companies because of
看到人们因为
this it's just very rude one thing that
这只是很粗鲁的一件事
people sometimes say that you should
人们有时会说你应该
never say right is welcome please come
永远不要说对，欢迎来
in and deploy this kubernetes cluster so
并部署此kubernetes集群，以便
you can test anything right nothing is
你可以测试任何东西，没什么是
more insulting or rude nothing says I
更侮辱或无礼我什么也没说
don't like you more than having to
不喜欢你，不必
deploy a whole production system just to
部署整个生产系统只是为了
be able to like I can't run slack do you
能够喜欢我不能懈怠吗
think I can run your kubernetes cluster
认为我可以运行您的kubernetes集群
no no no no no no no so that's not an
不，不，不，不，不，所以那不是
option not an option so instead what I
选择不是选择，而是我
want is some way to mock out this other
想要是某种可以嘲笑对方的方法
service the service that I'm making a
服务我正在做的服务
call to okay one way to do that is to
呼吁做某事的一种方法是
use wire mock so I can say on my test
使用电线模拟，所以我可以在测试中说
auto-configure wire mach port equals
自动配置的线马赫端口等于
8080 and here I'll say wire mock dot
8080，在这里我将说一下线模拟点
stub for wire mock dot get wire mock
电线模拟点存根
this is not our API we didn't build this
这不是我们的API，我们没有构建
dot with we'll return wire mock a
点，我们将返回电线模拟一个
response dot with body and we'll create
响应点与身体，我们将创建
that in a second with header HTTP
一秒钟用HTTP标头
headers
标头
dot app content type equals media type
点应用内容类型等于媒体类型
application Jason value with status 200
状态为200的应用程序Jason值
and and that's and then we need the body
那就是然后我们需要身体
so we'll provide the body there and the
所以我们将在那里提供尸体
body will be a string and now I'm gonna
身体将是一个字符串，现在我要
create I'm gonna just use auto configure
创建我要使用自动配置
JSON right so auto configure JSON I'm
JSON对，所以我自动配置JSON
gonna inject a Jackson object mapper
将注入一个Jackson对象映射器
it's gonna be a little longer so we're
它会更长一点，所以我们
gonna inject an object mapper here and
要在这里注入对象映射器
we're gonna use the object mapper to
我们将使用对象映射器
create instances of our records okay and
创建我们的记录实例好吧，
in order to do that I'm gonna pass in
为了做到这一点，我要传递
two records here new reservation one
这里有两笔新预订记录
Jane new reservation to Joe okay so I've
简（Jane）对乔（Joe）的新保留，好吧，我已经
got some JSON there JSON and I'm gonna
那里有一些JSON，而我要
use the JSON like this and do you notice
使用这样的JSON，您是否注意到
that I call it JSON because JSON is
我称之为JSON，因为JSON是
there's two there's JSON and then
有两个JSON，然后
there's Jason Jason is somebody's name
有杰森（Jason）杰森（Jason）是某人的名字
right that's a very interesting date
对，这是一个非常有趣的约会
hennifer I think crazy that joke from
亨妮弗，我觉得疯了
the Python community a very funny guy
Python社区一个非常有趣的家伙
anywho Doe so there we go I'm gonna now
任何人Doe所以我们要走了
run this okay
运行这个好吧
and expectation matches reservation oh I
和期望匹配保留哦我
guess it's wrong wrong way around isn't
猜错是不是
it ah yeah
是啊
one two there we go
一两个我们去
probably probably better if I just fix
如果我修复的话可能会更好
that so it's consistent whoa okay so now
所以这是一致的哇，好吧，现在
one
一
- always good to be consistent okay
-始终保持一致很好
three let's try that again one more time
三，让我们再试一次
so it looks like it's green right thing
所以看起来好像是绿色的正确的事情
is a green here and things are green and
这里是绿色，事物是绿色的
the producer side everything should be
生产者方面一切都应该
great and yet there's a bit of a bit of
很好，但还有一点
a wrinkle isn't there bit of a fly in
没有皱纹
the ointment isn't there because if you
软膏不在那里，因为如果你
look at this you see I've got this field
看看这个，你看到我有这个领域
called reservation name but I don't have
叫保留名，但我没有
a reservation name on the producer side
生产者方的保留名称
on the server right I just have name and
在服务器上，我只有名字和
that's a very dangerous situation to be
那是非常危险的情况
in we've got two different teams working
我们有两个不同的团队在工作
on different things and one side is
在不同的事情上，一方面是
working and everything's green on their
工作正常，一切都绿了
side and the other side everything's
另一边的一切
green as well and there's an end so it
也是绿色的，所以有终点
looks like we're all everything's gonna
看起来我们所有的一切
be fine let's just let's just deploy it
很好，我们只是部署它
it'll be fine right
没事的吧
this isn't PHP we can't just discover
这不是PHP，我们不能仅仅发现
the stuff in production right we need to
我们需要的生产权中的东西
do better and so one thing that people
做得更好，一件事，人们
do is they create integration tests
他们是创建集成测试吗
that's where the you know you start
那就是你知道你开始的地方
deploying companies clusters and of
部署公司集群和
course you can't run it on your local
当然你不能在本地运行
machine so you have a shared server or
机器，因此您拥有共享服务器或
services or cloud cluster that your
您的服务或云集群
organization uses for integration
组织用于集成
testing and then of course you have to
测试，然后当然必须
wait for people to be free or to be done
等待人们自由或完成
with it or you can spit up your own in
用它，或者你可以吐自己的
which case you've got this crazy cost
在这种情况下，您要为此付出疯狂的代价
no no gets to be very painful very
不，不，非常痛苦
quickly right especially if everybody
快速正确，尤其是如果每个人
has an isolated copy of their whole
有一个整体的孤立副本
multi-tenant distributed cloud so I want
多租户分布式云，所以我想要
to get fast feedback but I want to avoid
获得快速反馈，但我想避免
spending too much time in the
花太多时间在
integration test layer remember when you
集成测试层记得当你
have a testing pyramid 80% of it should
有一个测试金字塔80％应该
be very fast feedback yet like unit
反馈很快，却像单位
tests and mock tests like this and then
测试和模拟测试，然后
at the top you should have slower but
在顶部，你应该慢一点，但是
more exhaustive and more comprehensive
更详尽，更全面
integration tests and you know end to
集成测试，您知道最终
end tests and things like that smoke
最终测试之类的东西冒出来
tests so we want fast feedback and I
测试，所以我们需要快速反馈，我
don't want to give up that productive
不想放弃那种有生产力的
productivity but I've discovered a
生产力，但我发现了
problem here if this was a monolith and
这里的问题，如果这是一个整体
I changed the field in the monolith the
我改变了整体的领域
compiler would tell me but I don't have
编译器会告诉我，但我没有
a compiler for my Network API and so
网络API的编译器等
what I want is some way to capture that
我想要的是某种捕获方式
and then define that incompatibility in
然后在其中定义不兼容
my tests a good way to do this is with
我的测试执行此操作的好方法是
contracts consumer-driven contracts so
签订以消费者为导向的合同
what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna go back
我要做的是回去
to my producer here and I'm gonna use
给我的制片人，我将使用
spring cloud contract to describe how
春季云合约描述如何
this API should work a contract a
该API应该与合同
contract a contract is a thing that that
签订合同
a gets turned into a test right so I'm
一个变成正确的测试，所以我
gonna say should return all reservations
要说应该退还所有保留
groovy and it's just gonna be a thing
时髦，这将是一件事情
that I've got a map location I'm gonna
我有一个地图位置
say contract dot make and I'll say
说合同点制造，我会说
description
描述
reservations so I'm using goofy here too
预订，所以我也在这里用傻瓜
as a DSL I'm describing how data should
作为DSL，我正在描述数据应如何
be discussed should look basically how
讨论应该基本上看起来如何
an interaction with my API should look
与我的API的交互应该看起来
I'm saying when somebody makes a request
我是说有人提出要求时
to the server to the producer at for
到服务器到的生产者
such reservations using HTTP method get'
使用HTTP方法的此类保留get'
then I expect to have status 200 and
那么我希望状态为200，
expect to have headers including the
期望包含的标头包括
content type and I want the content type
内容类型，我想要内容类型
to be equal to application Jason value
等于应用Jason值
right and I want the body to have the
对的，我希望身体拥有
following shape okay so that body is
跟随形状好，以便身体
going to be a JSON structure and I can
将成为JSON结构，我可以
use a string here if I wanted to but I
如果我想在这里使用一个字符串，但我
have this nice object literal syntax and
有这个不错的对象字面量语法和
goofy that looks kind of like JSON so I
看起来像JSON的高飞，所以我
can just do that instead so here we go
可以代替它，所以我们开始
all right and then Joe and voila okay so
好吧，然后乔和瞧，好吧
there's my there's my contract now a
有我的合同，现在有
contract is only useful if something
合同仅在某些情况下有用
enforces it remember this is going to be
强制它记住这将是
compiled into a test it's gonna be
编译成测试会
transpiled into a unit test okay so I'm
转换成单元测试好了，所以我
gonna use a plug-in to do that work and
将使用插件来完成这项工作，
to force this test to get executed every
强制该测试每次执行
single time I build my producer desk
一次建立生产台
misc depths contract spring cloud
杂项深度合同春天云
contract depths okay
合同深度还可以
I'm gonna go here to my build section
我要去这里我的构建部分
build plugin and I'm adding the spring
构建插件，我要添加Spring
code contract maven plugin and I'm also
代码合同Maven插件，我也是
telling this plugin whenever you create
每次创建时告诉此插件
a test out of my contracts extend that
我的合同中的一项测试扩展了
test from the base class and the reason
从基类测试和原因
that we need to do that is because oh
我们需要这样做是因为哦
sorry this goes in the producer side not
抱歉，这不在生产者方面
the consumer the reason we want to do
消费者我们想要做的原因
that is because we want to know that
那是因为我们想知道
what we are doing is actually going to
我们正在做的实际上是
have the set up logic that we saw before
具有我们之前看到的设置逻辑
so did I have the contract here no
我在这里有合同吗
source test wheeze I didn't come okay
源代码测试喘息，我还没来
here we go put that here so a sourced
在这里，我们把它放在这里
test resources contracts there we go
测试资源合同，我们去了
okay so I've got now in the producer
好吧，现在我要担任制片人
side on the server side I've got this
在服务器端，我有这个
contract it's going to extend this class
合同，它将扩展该课程
called base class which I've configured
我配置的称为基类
in the plugin here base class and I need
在这里的基础类的插件中，我需要
to create that here in the test folder
在测试文件夹中创建它
so base class and this base class is
所以基类，这个基类是
just going to be a place where I do the
只是要成为我做的地方
same kind of set up logic that you saw
您看到的那种设置逻辑
me do before but it's gonna be available
我以前做过，但它将可用
for this generated test instead so it'll
对于这个生成的测试，所以它将
be a run with spring runner class it'll
参加春季跑步者班
be a spring boot test sure it'll have
做一个 spring boot 测试，确定它会
some properties including server type
一些属性，包括服务器类型
port equals 0 and I'm going to say a web
端口等于0，我要说一个网
environment equals random okay and we're
环境等于随机好吧，我们
gonna say that the config class is going
要说的是配置类
to use the reservation HTTP
使用保留HTTP
configuration class among other things
配置类以及其他
right or actually we don't even need
对的或者实际上我们甚至不需要
that but that'll that'll work okay and
那样，那样就可以了，
then we're going to do as we did before
然后我们将像以前一样做
we use mock bean to create the
我们使用模拟 bean 来创建
reservation repository and we're going
预订资料库，我们要去
to inject the local server port and
注入本地服务器端口并
we're gonna do some basic setup so
我们将进行一些基本设置，以便
here's my HTTP test okay so same as
这是我的HTTP测试，与
before put that in there and we're gonna
在把它放进去之前，我们要
say rest assured that base URI equals
说放心，基本URI等于
HTTP localhost plus this dot port so I'm
HTTP本地主机加上此点端口，所以我
now configuring all base logic all code
现在配置所有基本逻辑所有代码
that extends that did I miss anything
延伸到我错过了什么
let's make sure I didn't miss anything
确保我没有错过任何事情
we don't have a sorry oh yeah thank you
我们没有后悔哦，是的，谢谢
whoo all right good stuff I'm missing
谁好，我想念好东西
something kind of important here I feel
我觉得这里很重要
like and so just to be a hundred percent
喜欢，所以只是百分之一百
sure I'm gonna cheat a little bit base
确定我会作弊
class you have a import okay I didn't
上课你有进口，好吧，我没有
need that okay fair enough fair enough
需要足够的公平
I had that I had that and I was like I'm
我曾经拥有过那个，我就像我
not sure if that's real or if I need
不知道这是真的还是我需要
that but you know
那但你知道
if I did it before it's probably a
如果我在那之前做过
reason okay so now let's try it let's go
原因好吧，现在让我们尝试吧
to the producer downloads producer may
给制作人下载制作人可以
even clean install actually before I do
甚至在我之前干净安装
that dot m2 repository calm example may
那点m2仓库平静的例子可能
even clean install take some coffee okay
即使干净安装也可以喝点咖啡
what do we got stubs could not be found
找不到什么存根
source test resources contracts okay
源测试资源合同还可以
fingers crossed eyes crossed good stuff
手指交叉的眼睛交叉的好东西
okay so we can see it compiled
好吧，我们可以看到它已编译
everything is fine you can see that
一切都很好，你可以看到
installed the jar and the Maven palm
安装了罐子和Maven手掌
that xml and most importantly it
该xml，最重要的是
installed this thing called stubs and
安装了这个叫做存根的东西，
the stubs contains a file that our
存根包含一个文件，
consumer will consume you can see that
消费者会消费，您可以看到
it created a fake test for us right so
它为我们创建了一个假测试，所以
verifier i guess let me see it like this
验证程序，我想让我这样看
verifier test dot java
验证者测试点Java
okay well find CD target find it's in
好吧，找到CD目标，找到它了
the when the producer is still right so
当制作人仍然正确时
in the producer okay contract verifier
在生产者好的合同验证器中
test
测试
okay so contract verifier okay Yahveh
好吧，所以合同验证者好吧Yahveh
good and if we look at this file on the
很好，如果我们在
producer side you can see that that's
生产者方面，您可以看到
actually just a unit test that was
实际上只是一个单元测试
created for us by the compiler and it
由我们为它创建的编译器
has the same specification as our
与我们的规格相同
contract it says it's gonna be 200
合同说要200
applications Azon it'll have an ID equal
应用程序Azon的ID等于
to one a name equal to jane another one
一个名字等于简的名字
named joe and so on and that's been
叫乔，依此类推
communicated it's now in the maven
沟通现在在行家中
repository it could be Nexus or
可能是Nexus或
artifactory or whatever but it's in my
人工制品或其他任何东西，但它在我的
local m2 repository now on the client
客户端上的本地m2存储库
side I can get rid of this okay I'm
我可以摆脱这种困扰，我是
gonna get rid of wire Mach because I
会摆脱电线马赫，因为我
don't need wire luck because it was it
不需要运气，因为就是这样
was testing the wrong thing now I'm
我正在测试错误的东西
gonna use the stub Runner and here I'm
要使用存根转轮，我在这里
gonna tell the stub Runner go to maven
告诉存根赛跑者去行尸走肉
find the producer artifact find the
找到生产者工件找到
latest version of it plus means latest
它的最新版本加上意味着最新
version and run the resulting definition
版本并运行结果定义
on port 8080 and also I want you to look
在8080端口上，我也想让你看看
in local class path not in artifactory
在本地类路径中而不在人工环境中
not in in your class path but in the
不是在你的课堂上，而是在
local m2 repository and if we do
本地M2存储库，如果我们这样做
everything correctly and if the contract
一切都正确，如果合同
has the same shape as our client API
与我们的客户端API具有相同的形状
expects then this should work let's see
期望然后这应该工作，让我们看看
if it catches our bug right let's see so
如果它赶上了我们的错误，让我们看看
there is the data we got names back
有我们得到名字的数据
expect next matches it says reservation
期待下一场比赛说预订
name equals null so it failed right we
名称等于null，所以它失败了，我们
know why it failed let's go fix this our
知道为什么失败了，让我们去解决这个问题
client-side should say name rebuild this
客户端应该说名称重建
now okay and we have to fix that get
现在好了，我们必须修复该问题
name get name and we start the test cool
名字取名字，我们开始测试很酷
all right my friends so hopefully you
好吧，我的朋友们，希望你
got a feeling for what it means to write
对写什么意味着一种感觉
code that is testable to go fast to get
可测试的代码可以快速获得
to move to a place where we can use
移到我们可以使用的地方
test-driven development to isolate parts
测试驱动的开发以隔离零件
of our system including distributed
我们的系统包括分布式
systems including distributed services
包括分布式服务的系统
there are talks on spring cloud contract
有关于春季云合约的会谈
there's talks on testing with Andy
关于与Andy进行测试的讲座
Wilkinson there are talks on a lot of
威尔金森（Wilkinson）有很多关于
this stuff in-depth interactive
这些东西深入互动
programming of course so go see those
当然编程，所以去看看那些
thank you so much for coming I
非常感谢您的光临我
appreciate it
欣赏它
[Music]
[音乐]